My name is Zeibra Lemley with the Different Vibe True Beauty and Barber Salon and in this segment I'm going to show you how to do pigtails or otherwise known as Willie Nelson braids.
In the case of making a good pigtail, just to make sure that the hair is parted straight down the center.
So the hair can be evenly distribute on both sides.
You don't want a pigtail that one's better than the other.
So we're going to slice that here straight down the middle, making sure each side is evenly distribute.
When you comb it through, you're going to gather all the hair in your hand.
You're going to comb straight through 'till you make a, like a pigtail.
And to keep it this braid is to make sure that the hair, you start to braid at the nape of the neck.
Now I'm going to take the hair and I'm going to slice it off to three sections; a section for my right hand, a section for my left hand and there's a section in the middle.
Start to braid, I'm going to take the hair thats in my right hand and I'm going to cross it under to my hair in my left hand.
I'm going to take the hair in the middle and I'm going to bring it over to the second, with the first section was and I'm going to take the hair in the left hand and I'm going to cross it under.
I'm going to keep doing this until I get all the way down to the end of the braid.